Previously on Haven...
前情提要
You're the ones that have been kidnapping people, messing with the troubles. Why?
就是你一直在绑架别人 惹异能者 为什么?
Audrey Parker.
Audrey Parker
You don't get to threaten Audrey.
轮不到你来威胁Audrey
You.
你
You put that mark on those people.
就是你在别人身上留下印记
They're inferior. All of 'em.
他们全都是低等级的生物
Them, not us.
他们 不是我们
This isn't actually about some stupid trouble. This is about us.
这跟什么狗屁异能其实没多大关系 跟咱俩有关系
I love you, and you love me too.
我爱你 你也爱我
There isn't any part of me that will ever love you.
每个我都绝对不可能会爱上你.
Not Audrey Parker.
Audrey Parker是不会
And not Lexie or any other Haven-savers, but there's someone else in there.
Lexie也不会 其他来拯救港湾的身份也不会 可你内心深处还有一个人
And she is mine.
而她是我的
Let's move.
走起来
Clear the way.
让开
Hang on, susie. I'm right with you.
挺住 Susie 我陪着你
She's gonna be okay, right? The hospital's expecting her.
- 她会没事的 对吧? - 医院在等她
I love you, susie. That's my girl.
我爱你 Susie 好姑娘
Don't worry, cliff. I'll be all right.
别担心 Cliff 我会没事的
It's William.
是William
He's one step ahead of us again.
他又快了我们一步
Well, that sucked.
好吧 真不爽
What happened? Are you okay?
怎么了? 你没事吧?
Yeah, picked up a few stragglers and took 'em to higher ground.
嗯 接了几个落单的 带去高处了
How the hell did this happen?
这是怎么发生的啊?
Doreen hanscomb... the librarian?
Doreen Hanscomb...图书管理员?
Before William put her trouble on steroids,
在William激发她的异能之前
she'd remember her trip to Hawaii and she'd get sand in her shoes.
她记得她去夏威夷的旅行 鞋子进沙
Now, a volcano erupts.
现在 火山爆发了
All right, I'm gonna go call Jennifer, make sure she's okay.
好 我去打给Jennifer 确保她没事
Let's go home.
我们回家吧
William.
William
He's changing the troubles, and we don't know any of the rules.
他正在改变异能 而我们根本不懂规则
And we have nothing.
我们也一无所获
What?
干吗?
Your hair.
你的头发
This.
这个
It's nice to see Audrey again.
很高兴再见到Audrey
But the real question is...
但真正的问题是...
Who does William think that I am?
William以为我是谁?
Well, uh, he certainly thinks there's something between you two,
好吧 他肯定认为你们间有些什么
but he's wrong.
但他错了
Of course.
当然了
What?
怎么了?
There's a trouble...
你的床上...
In your bed. No.
- 有异能 - 不
Yeah, I think we should check it out.
嗯 我认为我们应该去看看
I want you to have a look in there.
我要你去看看
Nathan?
Nathan?
What?
什么?
William.
William
This is why I don't get pedicures.
所以我才不想修脚
No, no, no. Where is my car?
不 不 不 我的车子呢?
Man.
天啊
Just got that car.
把车开走了
Hello?
有人吗?
So the gull is now a bait shop.
所以灰鸥酒吧现在是鱼饵店了
BAIT SHOP I live in a bait shop.
我住在鱼饵店里
God.
天啊
Right, this way. Okay.
嗷 好 这边 好
All right.
好吧
Seriously, so over this.
说真的 受够了
What kind of trouble takes my shoes?
什么异能会弄走我的鞋子啊?
Oh, thank God.
噢 谢天谢地
What? Ma'am?
- 什么? - 女士?
What are you doing out here?
你在这里干吗?
Is this a joke? I don't know, you tell me.
- 整蛊呢? - 我不知道 你告诉我啊
You're the one walking around in your pajamas with no shoes on.
是你穿着睡衣不穿鞋在走路
You okay? You need some help?
你没事吧? 你需要帮助吗?
Duke, come on.
Duke 行了
You know my name?
你知道我的名字?
Yeah. I'm Audrey.
是啊 我是Audrey
Audrey Parker.
Audrey Parker
You don't know me.
我不认识我
Okay, I'm gonna assume that you don't have any I.D. On you.
好吧 我想你身上没带证件了
No, I don't have any I.D. On me.
没 我没带
So, Ms. Parker, where you heading?
那么 Parker小姐 你要去哪?
Well, I was heading to Haven pd to find Nathan.
好吧 我要去港湾警局 找Nathan
Nathan Wuornos.
Nathan Wuornos
There is no Wuornos at Haven pd. You wanna try again?
港湾警局没有姓Wuornos的 再试试?
Okay, listen, this has gotta be some kind of Haven thing, all right?
好 听着 这肯定又是港湾的异常了 好吧?
I woke up this morning, and everything's different.
我今早醒来 一切都不同了
You're a cop... you look good as a cop, but you're still a cop.
你是警察...你当警察挺帅的 但你居然是警察
The gull, it isn't the gull.
灰鸥酒吧不是灰鸥酒吧了
Let's get in the car, and we'll sort all this out.
咱们上车把这事搞清楚了
You're not really making any sense right now.
你现在说的话根本没道理
You know about this town, though, right? Ma'am, I know everything about this town.
- 你知道这个镇子的问题 是吧? - 女士 我知道这个镇子的一切
I'm third-generation Haven pd.
我是港湾警局的第三代了
Come on, let's get you off the side of the road.
走吧 带你上路了
Come on. Let's go.
快 走吧
It's all right. You're gonna be fine.
没事 你会没事的
Yep, that's right.
嗯 没错
Just hop in the back of the car for me. Back?
- 上车后座吧 - 后座?
Seriously, Duke, I think that something happened to you.
说真的 Duke 我觉得你出了问题
Says the woman who's walking around in her pajamas.
穿着睡衣到处走的女人如是说
Okay, listen, if you're a cop, then why don't you take me to the station?
好 听着 如果你是警察 你何不带我到局里?
You Haven't broken any laws, and I have to make an urgent stop.
你没有犯法 而我有急事
If you agree to get a psych evaluation at the hospital, I will help you out.
如果你同意到医院进行精神评估 我就愿意帮你
We will get you some shoes to start with, and I will help you try to find your friend. Yes.
- 先给你穿上鞋子 我会帮你找朋友 - 好
But first, I need you to wait in the car,
但首先 我要你在车里等着
so I can go take this witness statement.
我才能录目击证人口供
Vandalism? That's what you're worried about?
肆意毁坏? 你就担心这种事?
I know.
我知道
This town is going to hell.
这个镇子要下地狱了
If I leave you here, you gonna take off on me?
如果我放你在这儿 你会跑掉吗?
Won't get very far.
走不远的
Yeah.
嗯
Wait in the car.
车里等着
Vince!
Vince!
Dave!
Dave!
I'm sorry. Have we met?
不好意思 我们见过吗?
My dear, what ever happened to your shoes?
亲爱的 你的鞋子怎么了?
It's... it's me, Audrey.
是...是我啊 Audrey
Oh, my. I understand what's happening now.
天啊 我理解现在是怎么了
You do? Oh, fantastic, fantastic.
是吗? 噢 好极了 好极了
Haven has its first homeless person.
港湾有了第一个无家可归的人
Vandalism and now vagrancy. Guys, listen.
- 肆意毁坏 现在又有流浪者 - 两位 听着
I know about the troubles.
我知道异能(麻烦)的事
My dear, this is Haven.
亲爱的 这里是港湾
There's never been any trouble here.
才不会有什么麻烦呢
Welcome to HAVEN."The Safest Town In Maine" Oh, my God.
我的天啊 (欢迎来到港湾 缅因州最安全的镇子)
The troubles are gone.
异能消失了
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==- 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 港湾 第四季第10集
-==http://www.ragbear.com==- 港湾 第四季第10集
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 时间轴：TITI
-=破烂熊字幕组=- 翻译：亚特 校对：酒囊饭袋 时间轴：TITI
Well, the nurses say you're okay.
护士说你没事
A doc's gonna have to sign off before you're officially released,
正式放你走之前 医生会签文件的
but, uh, yeah.
不过 呃 是啊
Were you able to find out anything?
你能查出什么吗?
Nobody named Nathan Wuornos has ever lived in Haven.
没人叫Nathan Wuornos 或是住在港湾的
I'm sorry. That's okay.
- 抱歉 - 没关系
You know, I'll find him. Always do.
我会找到他 一直都这样
Look, um, I don't know exactly what you're going through, but, uh,
听着 我不想知道你究竟遇到什么事了 不过
well, you certainly don't have to do it alone.
你肯定不用一个人面对
I'm here if you need to call. That's my cell.
我随叫随到 那是我的手机号
I still can't believe you're a cop.
我还是不敢相信你是警察
It's the hair, right? Yeah, the chief hates it too.
发型问题对吧? 嗯 局长也不喜欢
And so you keep it.
你还留着
Yeah.
- 是啊 - 嗯
You might wanna be careful that you don't get fired.
你还是小心点别被炒了
Oh, that's not likely.
哦 不太可能
The chief is my dad.
局长是我爸
Doctor's ready for you now.
医生现在准备好了
Okay, well, um, thanks for everything.
那好 谢谢你所做的一切
Meeting you was really unexpected.
呃...见到你真是意料之外
Well, the feeling's mutual.
好吧 彼此彼此
Stay safe. Right.
- 注意安全 - 好
Okay.
好了
Ms. Parker, I'm Dr. Hansen.
Parker小姐 我是Hansen医生
Nathan.
Nathan
Nathan... Hansen.
Nathan...Hansen
Right, your father was Max Hansen.
对哦 你爸是Max Hansen
You knew him? Sort of.
- 嗯哼 你认识他? - 算是吧
Please.
请坐
Uh, sorry.
呃 不好意思
Have... have we met?
我...我们见过吗?
Technically yes, but actually not really.
呃 严格来说见过 但其实并没有
So, no. No.
所以 没有 没有
You're a doctor?
你是医生?
That's what they tell me.
人们是这么说的
Well, your test came back clear, and, uh, the nurse said you were lucid.
你的检测显示没问题 呃 护士说你神志不清
But do you mind?
- 但是 不介意吧? - 没事
So they found you wandering on the highway?
他们发现你在公路上乱走?
I was walking. I was not wandering. That's an entirely different thing.
我在走路 不是乱走 完全不同的两件事
Where were you walking to?
嗯哼 你走去哪里啊?
Was looking for someone, but I-I found him.
在找人 但我...我找到他了
Good.
好
The report says that you kept repeating there's some trouble that you needed to fix.
报告提到你一直在说要搞定什么异能
The trouble that I was worried about, it fixed itself.
我所担心的异能会自己修复
Good. Everything is... Perfect.
- 很好 - 一切都很...完美
Okay, Ms. Parker.
好 Parker小姐
Audrey Parker, but you... you can just call me Parker.
Audrey Parker 但你...你叫我Parker就行了
Okay, Parker, you're free to go.
好 Parker 你可以走了
Great.
- 很好 - 嗯哼
This may sound a little weird, but are you doing anything later tonight?
可能听起来很怪 但你今晚有安排吗?
Code blue, room 305.
紧急情况 305病房
Excuse me.
不好意思
All right, I can feel the tear.
好 我能感受到撕裂了
Yeah, hemostat now.
嗯 止血钳子
Okay, let's get him into surgery.
好 带他去手术室
Boy, am I glad to see you.
天啊 真高兴见到你
Has this day been freaky or what?
今天真是怪了去了?
Okay, you need to stay right here Oh, let's think this through.
- 好 你得留在这儿 - 哦 我们想清楚了
Who's he gonna believe?
他会信谁呢?
Me or a girl who was here for a psych aluation?
我 还是一个来检查精神状况的姑娘?
What did you do to Haven? Please, I didn't do this.
- 你对港湾干了什么? - 拜托 我什么都没做
Somebody's trouble stranded us in this boring tourist trap.
某人的异能把我们弄进了这次无聊的敲竹杠之旅
You know what's going on?
你知道是怎么一回事?
You're immune to the troubles.
你对异能免疫
Just like you.
和你一样
I told you we were connected. No, we're not.
- 我都告诉你咱心有灵犀了 - 不 才没有
I gotta get you back to the old Haven, so you can remember who you really are.
哇 我得带你回旧港湾 你才能记住你是谁
And unfortunately, we're gonna need the old troubles to do that, right?
不幸的是 我们需要旧异能才可以做到 对吧?
Hey, there's daddy. Daddy!
- 嘿 是爸爸 - 爸爸!
Hey, there's my big girl. How you doing?
嘿 我的乖女儿 你好吗?
You guys good?
你们好吧?
Your Dr. douche has a family.
混蛋医生有家庭诶
Hi, beautiful.
- 嗨 美女 - 噢
So in love. Well, good for him.
- 好有爱 - 他真幸福
I'm glad he's happy.
我很高兴他幸福了
Haven is better without the troubles.
港湾没有异能会更好
Here's what you don't know.
这是你不知道的
Deep down... You like the troubles.
内心深处...你喜欢异能
Hell, you want the troubles.
见鬼 是你想要异能
I don't know what you're talking about.
我不知你在说什么
No, you don't, but you will.
不 你不知道 但你会知道的
And if you're not gonna help me bring the old Haven back...
而如果你不帮我把旧港湾带回来...
Then I'm gonna have to do it myself.
那我就得自己来了
And I won't be delicate about it.
我可不会轻手轻脚的
Don't get too comfortable being here.
别太习惯待在这儿了
I won't do it. It's irresponsible.
我不干 这不负责任
We could incite panic.
我们可能会引发恐慌
If Haven is being overrun by homeless bag ladies, the people have a right to know!
如果港湾满是流浪女人 人们有权知道!
Vincent. It's our journalistic duty.
- Vincent - 这是我们的记者职责
Since when are we journalists?
我们什么时候是记者了?
Afternoon, fellas.
下午好 伙计们
Oh, is this about placing an ad?
哦 想放广告吗?
I'm sorry, but we're in the middle of chasing a story.
不好意思 我们正在追踪一篇报道呢
Oh, sounds exciting.
噢 听起来好兴奋啊
No, I'm looking for someone actually, and I know you guys know everyone,
不 其实我是找人 我知道你们谁都认识
so I thought maybe you could help.
所以我想你们或许能帮忙
I'm awfully sorry, but we don't have a "missed connection" section
我很抱歉 但我们的先驱者报没有
here at the herald.
"失联"版面
Well, I'm sure you'll be able to help... One way or another.
好吧 我相信你们能够帮忙的...主动或是被动
Hi... no, that's fine.
嗨...不 没关系
I didn't think you'd call, but, um, I'm glad you did.
我没想到你会打来 但我很高兴你找我了
Did you find your friend that you were looking for?
找到你在找的朋友了?
Not exactly.
不算找到
You know, I meant what I said earlier.
我之前是说认真的
I really do wanna help you. That's why I'm here.
- 我真的想帮你 - 所以我才来了
Listen, Haven has a big problem.
听着 港湾有大问题了
You have seen the signs, right?
你看到路牌了 是吧?
This is the safest town in... No.
- 这是最安全的镇子... - 不
There's a situation that you need to be aware of.
你得注意一个情况
There is a man, he's extremely dangerous, and I don't think that you're ready for whatever he's planning.
有一个男人 他非常危险 我觉得你对他的计划没有做好准备
I know that we are a small town, but I know how to do my job.
等等 我知道我们是小镇 但我知道怎样做好我的工作
Listen, that's not what I meant, all right? Hpd needs to take precautions.
听着 我不是这个意思 好吧? 港湾警局需要防患于未然
You can't just be on defense with this guy.
你不能就防着这家伙
He's always a step ahead. I can help you.
他总是先别人一步 我能帮你
I can help you find him, I.D. Him, bring him in.
我能帮你找到他 确认他 抓到他
Okay.
好
I think I know what's going on.
我想我知道是什么情况了
You think I'm Barney fife because you are law enforcement too.
你觉得我是Barney Fife 因为你也是执法人员 (60-68年节目"安迪・格里菲斯秀"中的警察角色)
You know, I found an Audrey Parker in the FBI.
我发现了FBI里面有个Audrey Parker
But it wasn't you.
但不是你
You undercover?
你是卧底?
It's complicated. Oh.
- 一言难尽 - 哦
Listen, I know this guy.
听着 我知道这家伙
All right, who is he? His name is William.
- 好 他是谁? - 他的名字是William
William.
William
Does William have a last name?
William有姓吗?
Right.
好吧
Excuse me, I have to take this.
不好意思 我得接
Yeah, this is detective Crocker.
嗯 我是Crocker警探
I'll be right there.
我就到
What's wrong?
怎么了?
Haven just had its first murder in 42 years.
港湾发生了42年来的首次谋杀案
You knew this was gonna happen. Who's the victim?
- 你知道这事会发生了 - 受害者是谁?
You can see for yourself.
你可以自己去看
Vince.
Vince
And Dave.
还有Dave
I saw you talking to the two of them earlier.
我看到你之前跟他们聊天了
You knew them?
你认识他们?
In a way.
算是吧
Looks like Vince was taken by surprise.
看来Vince没有料到
Dave fought back.
Dave反击了
He was a tough old guy.
他是个厉害的老头
Blonde hair.
金发
William.
William
Listen, he is trying to set me up, okay?
听着 他是想陷害我 好吗?
He planted that there. I- I can explain everything.
他当时是计划好的 我...我可以解释一切
Yeah.
嗯
And you will.
你会的
Get up.
起来
Audrey Parker, you're under arrest.
Audrey Parker 你被捕了
We both know you don't have enough to charge me, and you can't hold me here indefinitely.
咱都清楚你不够证据指控我 你不能一直把我扣留在这儿
Well, Audrey Parker, I wouldn't have to hold you at all if you'd just be straight with me.
这个嘛 Audrey Parker 我可以根本不扣留你 如果你跟我说实话
Who are you, and what are you doing here?
你是谁 你来这里干吗?
Truth, huh?
真相 是吧?
Listen, what I'm about to tell you is gonna sound really...
听着 我要告诉你的事情会非常...
crazy. Yeah, I got it.
疯狂 好 我懂
This whole world... this isn't right.
这整个世界...这是不对劲的
My Haven, the real Haven, people can do things,
我的港湾 真正的港湾 人们能做一些事
supernatural things, and we call them troubles.
超自然的事情 我们称之为异能
So somebody's trouble turned everything into what it is now.
所以某个人的异能 把一切变成现在的模样
And only you know about this?
只有你知道这事?
Yes.
是的
And William.
还有William
And he's killing people to find the troubled person who can change this back.
他在杀人 以找到可以变回来的异能者
William, right.
William 好吧
Look... I tried to help you.
听着...我试过帮你的
But this... this is too much.
但这...这太夸张了
Okay, Duke, I know you.
好 Duke 我懂你
In my Haven, you're... you're the criminal.
在我的港湾 你...你是罪犯
Please. Yes, with the same long hair, and you... you do what you want.
- 得了吧 - 是的 一样的长发 你...你随心所欲
You live on a boat, for God's sake.
你住在船上啊 老天爷
A boat? Yeah.
- 船上? - 是啊
And we're friends.
我们还是朋友
We trust each other.
我们相互信任
We got another body.
又有尸体了
Does the name Doreen hanscomb mean anything to you?
Doreen Hanscomb这名字你知道吗?
Yes.
是
In my Haven, she was William's last experiment.
在我的港湾 她是William的上一个实验对象
He must have thought that she caused this with her trouble, but he was wrong.
他肯定以为她制造了异能 但他错了
Everything's still the same, so he killed her.
一切还是照旧 所以他杀了她
I've heard enough. No, listen!
- 我听够了 - 不 听着!
I'm not crazy, all right?
我没疯 好吧?
He's still out there. He'll keep doing this.
他还逍遥在外 他会一直杀下去的
You can't leave me in here.
你不能放我在这儿
Detective Crocker. Dr. Hansen.
- Crocker警探 - Hansen医生
You're my m. E. Today.
- 嗯哼 - 你是我今天的法医
- Yes. - Nice to meet you.
- 是的 - 很高兴认识你
Uh, we've met, actually.
呃 我们其实见过了
Do you remember?
你记得吗?
Third grade. Mrs. pryal's class.
三年级 Pryal老师的课上
You stole my han solo lunchbox.
你偷了我的韩・索罗午餐盒 (星球大战人物)
And I would like to file a formal report and...
我会提交正式报告 再...
I'm just kidding.
我开玩笑的
I like to joke, I'm...
我喜欢开玩笑 我...
you may remember that I broke my arm that year, sledding.
你可能记得那年我伤了手臂 滑雪橇
Had to be reset twice, hurt like hell.
不得不接了两次骨 痛死了
That is part of the reason that I became a doctor.
这也是我成为医生的部分原因
Okay, if I say that I remember you, will you stop talking?
好 如果我说我记得你 你能闭嘴吗?
Just kidding.
开玩笑的
You... you like to joke.
你...你喜欢开玩笑
So I guess I got the short straw at the hospital today.
我今天在医院抽签被抽中了
What would it take to get a full-time m. E. In this town?
在这个镇子 怎样才能有一位全职法医啊?
Well, a lot more murders.
更多的谋杀
Doc, you signed off on a woman earlier today, Audrey Parker.
医生 你今天放一个女人走了 Audrey Parker
You notice anything off about her?
你注意到她有什么不正常吗?
No comment.
不予评论
Doctor-patient confidentiality.
医患保密条款
I'm just... she seemed... she seemed to have a thing for doctors,
我就...她好像...她好像挺喜欢医生的
but she checked out fine.
但她没事
Yeah, well, there's no record of her in any system anywhere.
嗯 哪里也查不到她的记录
Oh, why are you so interested in her?
哦 你为什么对她那么感兴趣?
No comment.
不予评论
Knock, knock.
敲门 敲门
You got a visitor.
有访客了
It's your lawyer.
是你的律师
I don't have a lawyer.
我没律师啊
No, no, it's him. Arrest him.
不 不 是他 抓他
He's the murderer. You said she'd try that one.
- 他是凶手 - 你说她出过这招了
I know, right?
我知道 对吧?
Wish me luck.
祝我好运吧
I told him you were delusional.
我告诉他你脑子有病
Oh, come on.
噢 得了吧
Is that any way to look at the only person like you that you've ever met?
这是看到了你见过的唯一一个像你的人吧?
I am nothing like you.
我才不像你
I know this is hard, but someday, you're gonna look back on this and laugh.
我知道这很难 但总有一天 你回想这事 会笑的
- Laugh? - Yeah.
- 笑? - 是啊
You killed Vince and Dave.
你杀了Vince和Dave
I thought they'd lead me to the troubled person.
我以为他们能把我引向异能者
My bad.
我的错
Ah, and then Doreen.
啊 然后是Doreen
You thought it was her. Yeah.
- 你以为是她 - 是啊
Not her.
不是她
And now I'm back to square one.
而现在我回到原点了
Thing is...
问题是...
I hate the legwork.
我讨厌跑腿
You know, the suspects and the clues and the...
嫌疑人啊 线索啊...
It's just so time-consuming.
太浪费时间了
But I know someone who's really good at it.
但我认识一个很擅长这种事的人
Audrey Parker.
Audrey Parker
So you are gonna help me find the troubled person.
所以你 要帮我找出异能者
No.
不
I wouldn't help you, not in this world or any other.
我不会帮你的 在哪个世界都不会
Yeah, you will, 'cause if you don't, more people are gonna die.
嗯 你会帮的 因为如果你不帮 更多的人会死
And people that Audrey Parker cares about.
Audrey Parker关心的人
Don't do this. This is for your good.
- 别这样 - 这是为你好
And for you, I will do whatever it takes.
而为了你 我会不择手段
So I'm gonna give myself a little head start
所以我自己先去了
'cause you're a little cranky today.
因为你今天有点脾气火爆
Guard!
看守!
So when you getut of here, I'd hop to it.
所以你出来时 我会跳过来的
Good talk.
聊得挺开心
Thanks.
谢了
I've examined the body and, well, it wasn't an accident.
我验过尸了 不是意外
The killer broke her neck.
凶手弄断了她的脖子
How do you know it wasn't an accident?
你怎么知道不是意外?
That's how.
就是这样
"Nother. "
"Nother"
What do you think it means?
你觉得是什么意思?
I think it means "not her. "
我觉得是"不是她"
She wasn't killed here. They... somebody dumped the body.
她不是在这被杀 他们...有人弃了尸
What is this?
这是什么?
You see that underneath her fingernails? I don't know.
- 你看到她手指下的东西了吗? - 我不知道
It's not dirt.
呃...不是泥土
No.
不
It's fiberglass.
是玻璃纤维
That's strange.
- 哈 - 好奇怪
Well, I've got the time of death.
好吧 我查出死亡时间了
About four hours ago, give or take.
大概是四小时前
Four hours?
四小时?
No, that's not possible.
不 不可能
Let me check.
我想想哈
Yeah, it is.
没错 是这样
Audrey Parker was still in custody four hours ago.
四小时前Audrey Parker还被关着
Audrey Parker was your suspect?
Audrey Parker是你的嫌疑人?
No, I...
不 我...
Just... sorry.
就...不好意思
That's my wife.
我老婆
Hello, honey.
好 亲爱的
Honey? Marie?
亲爱的? Marie?
Marie?
Marie?
Hel... guess she hung up.
什...估计她挂电话了
Well, it's been great working with you.
和你共事很开心
I think we make a very good team.
我觉得我们是很好的团队
Come on.
起来了
Your hold is up.
拘留时间到
Your lawyer says that we have to let you go.
你的律师说我们必须放人了
All right, Stan, if that lawyer comes back here, don't trust him.
好 Stan 如果那律师回到这儿 别信他
Okay.
好吧
Get some help.
看医生吧
Nut job.
疯子
Wow, Nathan, nice house.
哇 Nathan 靓房啊
Oh, thank God you're all right.
噢 谢天谢地你没事
You. What's wrong?
- 你 - 怎么了?
Okay, whatever you want right now, I can't.
好 不管你现在想怎样 我无法奉陪
My family is miss What's...
- 我家人不见了 - 怎么...
I am calling the police.
我要报警
Oh, thank God. That's...
噢 谢天谢地 那是...
- that's my wife. - Good.
- 那是我老婆 - 很好
Thank God.
谢天谢地
Hi, honey, I... who is this?
嗨 亲爱的 我...你哪位?
It's someone named William. He wants to talk to you.
一个叫William的人 他想和你谈谈
William, don't hurt his family. Well, that part's up to you, Audrey.
- William 不准伤害他的家人 - 那就看你了 Audrey
You find me the troubled person that did this Haven, and I'll give the hansens back.
你给我找到把港湾弄成这样的异能者 我就交出Hansen母女
The hansens are innocent, all right? What do you want with them?
Hansen母女是无辜的 好吧? 你拿她们想怎样?
Well, you made it clear to me that you'd sacrifice your happiness by staying here.
你对我说明白了 你留在这 牺牲了自己的幸福
But I'm guessing you won't sacrifice. Nathan's happiness.
但我想你不会牺牲Nathan的幸福
Find the troubled person, or the hansens die.
找到异能者 不然Hansen母女死
See you soon.
很快再见
It went well.
很顺利
What the hell is going on?
究竟是怎么一回事?
Okay, we don't have time for that. I am calling the police.
- 好了 我们没时间说这个 - 我要报警
You cannot call the cops, okay?
你不能叫警察 好吧?
What? William wants to deal with me.
- 什么? - William想和我做交易
Anything you do is gonna put your family in jeopardy.
你有动静都会危及你的家人
Who are you?
你是谁?
How am I supposed to trust you? You don't have any other choice.
- 我凭什么信你? - 你没别的选择了
The person that William's looking for, we need to find him.
William在找的人 我们得找到
Who? Who is he looking for?
谁? 他在找谁?
The person he's looking for is... Special.
他在找的人是...很特别的
They may view this Haven as different or even bad.
他们看待港湾会不同 或者看得更糟
Is there anything weird you've noticed here lately?
你最近注意到这里有什么奇怪吗?
Weird? Is there anything that seems weird?
奇怪? 有没有奇怪的事情?
Uh, you mean other than the three murders
呃 你是说除了三宗谋杀案
and the fact that my wife and daughter have been kidnapped?
以及我老婆女儿被绑架?
There was nothing weird in Haven.
港湾没有怪事
There was no crime in Haven until you came. Yeah, except for the vandalism.
- 你来之前 港湾都没有犯罪 - 嗯 除了肆意毁坏
Vandalism? What? Since when?
肆意毁坏? 什么? 何时有的?
Wait, so that's new?
等等 所以那是新事?
What?
什么?
Are these your flyers?
这些是你的宣传单?
What? Who cares?
什么? 谁在意啊?
Yeah. Susie.
对了 Susie
In the old Haven, she was injured in an explosion.
在旧港湾 她在爆炸中受伤了
Where I'm from, she's married to cliff. But here she's with this guy.
在我那里 她嫁给了Cliff 但在这里她跟了这家伙
His face was sctched out on one of their signs.
他们的广告牌上 他的脸被刮花了
I need to talk to susie. There's an open house.
我得和Susie谈谈 是出售房屋
- Open house. - O...
- 出售房屋 - 出...
we gotta get to this open house.
我们得去这座出售房屋
We're going to an open house?
我们要去一座出售房屋?
I don't care that her hold was up! Do you understand that?
我不管是谁看着她的! 明白了?
She was my only lead!
她是我唯一的线索!
Get out of my way.
别挡路
Find her!
找到她!
Susie and I really think it's the time to jump in.
Susie和我真觉得是时候加入了
The Haven real estate market has never been hotter.
港湾房地产处在最热状态
Look, there he is again. Who is that guy?
- 看 又是他 - 那家伙是谁?
And why does he keep following us around? Cliff.
- 他为什么一直跟着? - Cliff
Look, just wait, okay? I'll handle this.
听着 等等 好吗? 我来处理
Cliff?
Cliff?
Hey, cliff, just hang... hang on.
嘿 Cliff 等...等一下
You know who I am? Yeah.
- 你知道我是谁? - 是啊
Yeah, I do, and I-I know that you're troubled.
嗯 我知道 我...我知道你是异能者
I always thought it was some dumb family joke, but it's real.
我以为是什么白痴家庭玩笑 但却是真的
Yeah. What happened?
嗯 发生什么了?
Susie got hurt back in old Haven because of the volcano troubles, remember?
Susie在旧港湾受伤了 因为火山异能 记得吗?
Right.
是的
Well, she died later that night.
她在当晚晚些时候去世了
So I wished for the troubles to go away.
所以我希望异能消失
I mean, it's just something you say, right?
我是说 只是嘴上说说 对吧?
I never thought it would happen, but then, poof.
我从没想过会发生 但接着 嘣
Trouble-free Haven. So wait, you just wished the troubles away?
- 没异能的港湾 - 等等 你希望异能消失?
Yeah.
是啊
My family always said there's a dark side to every wish.
我的家庭总说每个希望都有阴暗面
They were right because she's alive again,
他们说对了 因为她又活了
but she doesn't even know that I exist.
但她都不知道我的存在
Now she thinks I'm some kind of creep.
现在她以为我是某个怪人
I just wanted to see her again.
我只想再见到她
Why don't you just try wishing for something different?
你怎么不试试希望别的呢?
That could make things worse than they already are. It's like playing Russian roulette.
可能会比现状更糟糕 就像玩俄罗斯轮盘
The wishes come with a downside. Right.
- 希望都有不好的一面 - 是啊
At least she's alive again, and, well, it looks like she's happy, so...
至少她又活过来了 看来挺幸福的 所以...
Even if it's without me. But wait.
- 但如果是没有我... - 等等
Cliff, what happens if... if something happens to you?
Cliff 要是...如果是你出了事呢?
What happens to this version of Haven?
这个版本的港湾会怎样?
I don't know, it's not like I have some sort of manual.
我不知道 我也没有什么使用手册
We can't take any chances, all right? We're gonna get you out of here.
我们不能冒险 好吧? 我们要带你离开这儿
We're gonna keep you safe. Okay, what are we doing?
- 让你安全 - 好 我们在干吗啊?
Are we making some kind of exchange? No, we can't do that.
- 我们要进行某种交换吗? - 不 我们不能那样
My family... I will get them back.
- 我的家人... - 我会救回她们的
I promise you.
我向你保证
But for now, I mean, all William wants is me, so...
但现在 William想要的就是我 所以...
did you... did you call the police?
你...你报警了?
No. Just wait here.
没 在这等着
Duke stay out of this.
Duke 别掺和
If you think that Hansen needs protection, let me remind you that I am the cop here.
如果你认为Hansen需要保护 让我提醒你 我才是这里的警察
You have no idea what's going on. You don't even know where you are!
- 你不知发生了什么 - 你都不知你在哪里!
Okay, I am not crazy, all right?
好吧 我没疯 好吧?
William has been killing people to get to that... Nathan!
William一直在杀人去...
What are you doing?
你在干什么?
We gotta go. We're wasting time.
我们得走了 我们在浪费时间
Will you just stop and listen?
你能消停下来听我说吗?
Do people put up with this where you're from?
你那边的人受得了你吗?
Look, the dead newspaper men, Doreen hanscomb's murder,
听着 死亡的报界人士 Doreen Hanscomb被杀案
the note carved into her forehead...
刻在她前额的字...
all of that leads back to one common denominator, and that is you.
全都指向了一个导火索 就是你
Okay, I tried to warn you.
好 我试过警告你了
Yeah, you did.
是 你警告了
And I believe you.
我也信你
What?
什么?
If this William is fixated on you,
如果这个William盯着你不放
then, well, maybe we can use that to our advantage.
那么 或许我们可以因势利导
Now can you tell me, where is Hansen taking him?
你能告诉我 Hansen带他去哪?
- To William. - Okay.
- 到William那儿 - 好
You used Nathan's cell phone to find us, right?
你用Nathan的手机找到我们 是吧?'
You still got a signal? I sure do.
- 你还有信号吗? - 当然
Okay, then we can use that to track him.
好 那我们就能用来追踪他
You can fill me on the case details in the car.
你可以在车里跟我说说案件细节
Hey, you really believe me?
嘿 你真的信我?
You were right about the boat.
船的事你说对了
I always did want one.
我确实总想要一艘
Hey, doc, you okay?
嘿 医生 你没事吧?
Thanks for coming so quickly.
谢谢你这么快过来
You're gonna get your family back, all right?
你会救回家人的 好吗?
I just need your friend.
我只是需要你的朋友
I'm s... I'm sorry.
我...我很抱歉
It's okay, I would've done the same thing if it was my wife.
没事 如果是我老婆 我也会这么做的
Start walking.
走过来吧
It's okay.
没关系
- Oh, God. - It's okay, it's okay.
- 噢天啊 - 没事的 没事的
Come on, let's get you home. Come on.
走吧 我们回家 走
Come on.
走吧
Listen, I'm... I'm no good to you.
听着 我...我对你没好处
My wishes, they never turn out the way they're supposed to.
我的希望 总是没法如愿
- You wished for this place? - Yeah.
- 你希望有这样的地方? - 是啊
Okay, uh, then I'm gonna have to have you wish to have the old Haven back.
好吧 那我得让你希望 把旧港湾变回来了
No, no. No, I'll never do that.
不 不 不 我不干
Susie's dead there.
在那边Susie去世了
This is gonna be exhausting.
会很累了啊
What do you mean you're leaving, Nathan?
你说走了是什么意思 Nathan?
Set the alarm. The police are on their way. Tell them everything.
开警报 警察在路上了 把事情全告诉他们
Where could you possibly be going?
你还能去哪啊?
I put that man in danger.
我让那男人身陷险境了
I need to help him.
我得帮他
I'll be right back. Okay?
我会回来的 好吗?
Gun! Drop it! On the floor!
枪! 放下! 放地上!
No.
不
Kick it.
踢过来
Hey, hon.
嘿 亲
How are you?
你好吗?
I've had a rough day.
我今天过得很不顺
Let cliff go.
放Cliff走
Cliff's our ticket back to old Haven.
Cliff是我们回旧港湾的票
Look, William, we can all walk away from this.
听着 William 我们都可以脱身的
Let's just talk.
我们谈谈吧
You son of a bitch.
你个狗娘养的
Why did... don't move.
- 为什么... - 别动
I shouldn't have done that.
呃 我不该那么做的
And I am sorry.
我很抱歉
The thing is he doesn't matter.
问题是 他不重要
I mean, none of them matter.
他们都不重要
They matter.
他们重要
This place, it matters.
这个地方 重要
No. You only think that they do.
不 你以为而已
You gotta get this idea out of your head that you're some savior here to fix the troubles.
你不能再想自己是这里的救星 能纠正异能
The real you?
真正的你呢?
You made the troubles.
你制造异能
Why do you think you're the one who has to come back to Haven over and over?
你觉得为什么会是你 一遍又一遍地回到港湾?
Why do you think you're the one who has to deal with the troubles?
你觉得为什么会是你非得面对异能?
You made them.
你制造它们
You made the troubles.
你制造异能
You're being punished.
你在接受惩罚
That's what agent Howard said.
Howard探员就是这么说的
But no, that's... that's not true.
但不是 那...那不是真的
It is.
是真的
And, um... I know because we did it together and we liked it.
而且...我知道 因为是我们一起干的 我们也很享受
So just give him one of your little Audrey pep talks, fix this trouble, and take us home.
所以 给他一次你的Audrey激励谈话 纠正异能 带我们回家吧
Maybe... maybe what you're saying is true.
也许...你说的也许是真的
You know about us, about... The troubles, I just... I... I don't know who I am.
我知道我们...知道异能 我就...我...我不知我是谁
It's really scary, you know?
真的很可怕 你知道吗?
I just need you to be... can you just be patient with me?
我就是需要你...你能对我有耐心吗?
Freeze.
别动
Drop it.
放下
This might do the trick.
这样或许有用
Oh. Hey, you okay?
- 噢 - 嘿 你没事吧?
What happened?
发生什么了?
William.
William
We need to kill him.
我们得杀掉他
I'm just glad that you're still alive.
我很高兴你还活着
Vince and Dave too, of course.
当然还有Vince和Dave了
I was a cop. Yeah, a really good one.
- 我是警察 - 是啊 好警察呢
And William shot me? Mm-hmm, point-blank.
- William还开枪打我? - 嗯哼 打到胸口
Yeah, I'm gonna get a bigger gun.
嗯 我要换一把更大的枪
Thanks.
谢了
Susie died of complications last night. They found cliff shot dead.
Susie昨晚死于并发症 他们发现Cliff被枪杀
William got to him before he could untrouble Haven again.
William抢在他再次解除港湾的异能之前杀了他
Sorry. William can't get away with this.
- 抱歉 - William不能脱罪
Well, we know he's somewhere in Haven. Did you find out anything new about him?
好吧 我们知道他在港湾 你还知道他的什么新信息吗?
No. Nothing.
不 没有
But detective Crocker did mention that he found fiberglass on William's last victim.
但Crocker警探提到他在William的 最后一个受害者那里发现了玻璃纤维
It was... it was an industrial grade, like the kind that you build boats with.
是...是工业级别的 就像那种造船的
Which gets me thinking... Maybe he's using the same hideout.
- 让我想到... - 或许他在使用同一个藏身地
- Yeah. - Boathouse or repair shop.
- 嗯 - 船库或者维修店
Fiberglass boat repair.
玻璃纤维 船只维修
Okay, there's only three in the area. Well, he wouldn't wanna risk getting caught.
- 好 这片区只有三家 - 他不会冒被抓的风险
Which one's the furthest from where they found Doreen?
哪家是离发现Doreen的地方最远的?
Danny's dry dock, but, God, there's no number.
Danny的干船坞 但是 天啊 没有号码
That is because it's a cover.
因为那是伪装
Yeah.
是啊
Old man Jessup, he dries out his weed harvest there once a year.
老家伙Jessup 他每年去那里晒草一次
What? It's not my job to arrest him.
什么? 抓他又不是我的工作
Growing season's over.
嗯哼 生长季结束了
That makes it the perfect hideout. Nice work, detective Crocker.
- 那就成了完美的藏身地 - 干得好 Crocker警探
That hurts me.
很伤人
Okay, come on, guys. Let's go.
好了 走吧 两位 我们出发
- Shotgun. - Shotgun.
- 副座
Well, I thought you'd wanna finish our conversation.
我以为你想结束谈话
Just didn't think we'd have an audience.
没想到我们有观众啊
I didn't come here to talk.
我不是来聊天的
No.
不
You don't wanna shoot me.
你不想开枪打我
Hey, pal. She really does.
嘿 伙计 她确实想
But not for the reason you think.
但不是你以为的理由
Let me guess.
我猜猜
You didn't tell 'em.
你没告诉他们
Well, they have a right to know.
他们有权知道啊
Don't you think? About us?
你不觉得? 关于我们的?
Shut up!
闭嘴!
I like you guys.
我喜欢你们
So I'm gonna tell you everything you wanna know
所以你们想知道她是谁 她干了什么
about who she is and what she's done.
这些我全告诉你们
Sorry.
抱歉
What we did.
我们干了什么
Together.
一起
'Cause we are so connected.
因为我们太心有灵犀了
No!
不!
Audrey.
Audrey
What the.. you're all right, babe.
- 什么... - 你是对的 宝贝
What the hell's happening?
发生了什么啊?
It's the same wound.
一样的伤口
They are connected.
他们是相连的
Parker. Parker.
Parker Parker
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.ragbear.com==- 欢迎加入